nfohump.com 2019-05-08

# NFOHump

  * We will never sell, rent or otherwise distribute or make public your personal information.
  * We will not send Spam or any other unsolicited form of communication to you. We hate Spam just as much as you!
  * Your data will only be used to provide you this service and used only when absolutley necessary.

## Site visitation tracking

Cookies are used to enable this service, so that you can browse the forum, interact with other users and receive messages. Session cookies are used to enable you to login under your registered Username and to use this service for the duration of your visit. When the option "Remember me" is chosen upon login in Cookies will be used to remember your login for the next time you visit. 

Your current IP address is stored when logging in and it is used to check for any suspicious or unauthorized activity on your account. 

## Registering an account & participating in the forum

Should you choose to participate on our forum or leave a comment to any posts the information that you had entered on the registration page when creating your account, such as your nickname, email address and contact information will be used when making the said post along with the current time & date and your computer's IP address at the time of posting. 

The information you enter on the registration page when creating your account will be saved to this website's database. This information is only used to identify you as a contributor and is not passed on to any of the third party data processors or used for any other purpose. 

Your contributions (posts or comments) and it's associated personal data will remain on this site until we see fit to either 1.) remove the contribution or 2.) remove the thread or post containing the contribution for whatever reason. Should you wish to have the contributions and it's associated personal data deleted, please contact us here. 

If you are under 16 years of age you MUST obtain parental consent before registering and using our service. 

**NOTE: You should avoid entering personally identifiable information into any contributions that you make using our service on this website.**

## How the information is stored

Any contributions you make to this website, either by participating on the forum or by any other means are stored on this website's database and they are not encrypted. You may use HTTPS to access this website securely, but please consider any such contribution as insecure and refrain from leaving any kind of sensitive or personally identifiable information within. 

## About the Server that hosts this website

The website is hosted in Amsterdam in Netherlands. All access to the server is restricted to authorized personel only.
